saralweb.com 2010-10-18

# Saralweb : Free Classifieds Delhi India

---|---  
  
|  |   
---|---  
| |    
|  **  
SARALWEB.COM PRIVACY POLICY **  
---|---  

Your privacy is important to us, so Saralweb has created this Privacy Policy to explain how your information is protected, collected and used. This Privacy Policy applies to all Saralweb websites, including our publicly accessible web sites located at Saralweb.com ("Saralweb"). This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. You can always review the most current version at www.saralweb.com By using Saralweb, you consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future. If there is a conflict between our Terms of Use governing your use of the Sites and this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use control.  
Collection   
Information posted on Saralweb is obviously publicly available. Our servers are located in the United States (seattle). Therefore, if you choose to provide us with personal information, you are consenting to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers in the United States. We collect and store the following personal information: 

  * email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information. 
  * computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Saralweb and ad data (all through cookies - you can take steps to disable the cookies on your browser although this is likely to affect your ability to use the site) 
  * other information, including users IP address and standard web log information. 

Use  
We use users' personal information to: 

  * provide our services 
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; 
  * encourage safe trading and enforce our policies; 
  * customize users' experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;
  * communicate marketing and promotional offers to you; by publishing ads either online and/or in print, as the case may be, in connection with items that are for sale by customers 
  * to third party service providers and to affiliated entities in order to carry out work on our behalf, 
  * to law enforcement agencies for the purposes of investigating fraud or other offenses, or 
  * to legal, financial, and other professional advisors or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of its business or operations. 
  * By having your mobile number listed on saralweb.com, you agree to receive SMS from users who may wish to contact you. 
  * Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law. 

Cookies and IP Addresses  
we may use your IP address to identify you and your membership, gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose problems with our server, and administer the Site. The Site uses cookies to keep track of your membership tools. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. We also provide an option to log out should you be using an insecure or publicly shared computer. 

We use outside ad companies to display ads on the Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of the Site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. 

Links  
This Site contains links to other websites, such as websites providing national search capabilities and information resources designed to inform buyers and sellers about general aspects of property that is being sold. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Please ensure you review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.   
Disclosure  
We don't sell or rent users' personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without users explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other's rights, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal information with: 

  * corporate affiliates who help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services. (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to).
  * service providers who help with our business operations. 

Using Information from Saralweb  
You may use personal information gathered from Saralweb only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that.   
Access, Modification, and Deletion   
You can see, modify or erase your personal information by reviewing your posting or account status page. Contact [ customer support ](mailto:support@saralweb.com) to review any personal information we store that is not available on Saralweb. There may a charge associated with such requests but these will not exceed the amounts permitted by law. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies; and prevent bad guys from coming back.   
Security  
We use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure, but as you probably know, nothing's perfect, so we make no guarantees.   
General   
We may update this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next post or after 30 days, whichever is sooner. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply. Send questions about this policy to [ support@saralweb.com](mailto:support@saralweb.com)   
Questions, Comments, Concerns   
If you have any questions or comments about our use of Personal Information, please contact us at [ support@saralweb.com](mailto:support@saralweb.com) .   
  
|   
---  
-:Catch us on:-  
|   
---  
Copyright 2010 TA Netgables Pvt Ltd. All Rights Reserved
